const STORE = [
    {
        question: 'In what year was Nintendo founded?',
        answer: [
            '1889',
            '1701',
            '2000',
            '1983',
        ],
        correctAnswer:'1889',
        explanation:"Nintendo was founded on September 23, 1889 by Fusajiro Yamauchi in Kyoto, Japan, as an Playing Card Company.",
    },
    {
        question: 'What video game has sold the most copies to date?',
        answer: [
            'Super Mario Bros.',
            'Call of Duty: Black Ops',
            'Grand Theft Auto V',
            'Tetris',

        ],
        correctAnswer:'Tetris',
        explanation: 'With an astounding 170 million copies sold, Tetris is by far the most sold game ever. The fact it was first put on sale over three decades ago helps',
    },
    {
        question:'What is the maximum score that can be reached in Pac-Man',
        answer: [
            '1,000,000',
            '5,000',
            '3,333,360',
            '9,640,100',
        ],
        correctAnswer: '3,333,360',
        explanation: 'The highest score you can get in Pac-Man is 3,333,360. This is achived doing the first 255 levels by eating every possible dot, power pellet, fruit, and enemy, without losing a single life, and using all extra lives. The first person to achieve this score was Billy Mitchell in 1999.',
    },
    {
        question:'What is the best-selling console of all time?',
        answer: [
            'PlayStation 2',
            'Nintnedo: NES',
            'Playstation 4',
            'Xbox 360',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'PlayStation 2',
        explanation: 'With 156 million units sold Playstation 2 is the best selling unit to date.',
    },
    {
        question:"From the famous Nintendo game , what is Mario's and Luigi's last name?",
        answer: [
            'Roberto',
            'Mario',
            'Pepperoni',
            'Angelo',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Mario',
        explanation: 'Their last name is Mario, Mario\'s full name is “Mario Mario”. As for Luigi, he\'s “Luigi Mario”. During Japan\'s 30th anniversary Super Mario Bros Shigeru Miyamoto cleared this up.',
    },
    {
        question:'Who is the main playable character name in the game Legend of Zelda?',
        answer: [
            'Ganondorf',
            'Zelda',
            'Link',
            'Sheik',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Link',
        explanation: 'Link is the main protagonist of Nintendo\'s video game series The Legend of Zelda.',
    },
    {
        question:'This famous cheat code “up, up, down, down, right, left, right, left, B, A, START” is known as what?',
        answer: [
            'The Konami Code',
            'Cheat Code',
            'The Contra code',
            'Code of Honor',

        ],
        correctAnswer: 'The Konami Code',
        explanation: 'This sequence of keystrokes is called "The Konami Code". It allows players to enable special features in video games made by the Japanese company Konami.',
    },
    {
        question:'What was Microsoft\'s first console?',
        answer: [
            'Xbox',
            'Dreamcast',
            'Gamecube',
            'Xbox 360',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Dreamcast',
        explanation: 'Okay this can be argumenting, although is was a partnership Microsft first console was the Dreamcast. On May 21, 1998, Microsoft proudly announced its partnership with Sega on the Dreamcast, the "ultimate home video game system". What started out as a coming together of two giants, one of gaming, one of computing, ultimately fizzled out into being nothing more than a memory.',
    },
    {
        question:'What was the longest time an individual has played a video game without any breaks?',
        answer: [
            '135 hours',
            '8 hours',
            '48 hours',
            '96 hours',
        ],
        correctAnswer: '135 hours',
        explanation: 'Determined by Okan Kaya which played Call of Duty: Black Ops 2 for a total of 135 hours. Thats more than five days!',
    },
    {
        question:'In what year was the first game in the Halo series released?',
        answer: [
            '2001',
            '2000',
            '2005',
            '1999',
        ],
        correctAnswer: '2001',
        explanation: 'The first game of the Halo franchise, it was released as a launch title for the Xbox gaming system on November 15, 2001.',
    },
];